A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
Subaki! Enchanted sword mode! Right!
A sound soul dwells within a sound body.
A sound body.
I'm falling down to my shadow.
Falling down to my shadow
息をひそめて
待っている the dream life
You're scary
君が望めば
どんな世界も
その目に映せるから
See you in your dreams, yeah, baby
怖い夢だとしても
テレブ君のために
星を砕ぎ
飾り付けた
Black paper, brown, brown
信じてくれたなら
When you lost him or young
Forever with your soul
見上げれば輝く
月のように
トーリー
キッド
It's not like it was my decision.
And I would really rather not talk about it, okay?
Yeah, fine.
But do you think you could at least give us an idea of where we're going?
Yeah, that's fair enough.
We're going to a place called Sarcophagus.
Sarcophagus?
That's right.
And it's aptly named, too.
And why's that?
It used to be just an ordinary old village like any other.
But that was 20 years ago.
Things have changed.
Changed how?
Well, one day, its citizens suddenly disappeared.
Every last one of them.
What?
How could all those people vanish in the thin air?
To this day, no one knows.
The people sent to investigate vanished just like the village's citizens, gone without a trace.
After a while, the investigation was given up.
It would have been too dangerous to continue.
The entire area was locked down to prevent further disappearances.
That's where we're going.
There it is.
That Sarcophagus.
The last magic tool.
Mission Impossible for Unarmed Kid?
See that?
That wall was hastily built.
Almost like the builders were desperately trying to cover something up before anyone saw it.
Like the Academy's doing now.
This place has given me the creeps.
Maybe we should forget the mission, huh?
I hope I see a monster!
Don't say stuff like that!
Are you crazy?
No, no, no!
Not happening!
I am not going in there!
You know I can't deal with creepy stuff!
I've even got a doctor's note that specifically says to avoid monsters!
You want to see it?
I'll show it to you.
You can calm down.
I'm not taking the two of you with me.
Seriously?
We don't know what caused the disappearances.
It could be a monster.
Or a virus.
Or maybe even some kind of chemical weapon.
But one thing we do know for sure.
No human who's ever gone in there has made it back out alive.
I can't risk taking you guys in there with me.
Not when I have no idea what we'd be up against.
It would simply be too dangerous.
Much as I hate to admit it, you've got a point there.
I'm guessing that's why Dad sent me instead of one of the other Meisters.
My Reaper body is less vulnerable than most.
Even so, this is still dangerous.
Yes, but what does that matter?
My Dad has made his policies on this clear.
Our top priority is the magic tools.
That's what you're after here?
If I'm not out in 40 minutes, head back for the Academy.
Go straight there.
You will not come in after me.
Instead of sending me out to help battle the Keisha, Dad gives me this mission.
Well, soon enough, I'll see what's so important about this tool.
We've lost contact with the 13th Squadron.
15 and 17, circle around and attack the enemy in Area 34.
It sounds like it's complete chaos out there.
All in all, I'd say it could be going better.
Maybe it's time for us to assume the command.
Then what are we supposed to say?
What orders do we give that will help them?
I don't know, but anything would be better than standing here doing nothing while they fight.
Well, that's where you got it wrong.
If we start giving random orders, we could stir up even more confusion.
No, not the scary face again.
Listen to you two.
Sometimes I envy your freedom.
You can go wherever you want, do whatever you want, whenever you want.
You can take real action.
You want chain here.
Know what I mean?
He's got a point.
At least we can leave.
I guess we're not the only ones who are frustrated.
If his soul wasn't bound to Death's city,
Lord Death would have been the first one on that battlefield fighting the Kisha.
Here we are.
The Vanishing Village.
So far I don't sense anything abnormal about this place other than its emptiness.
It's utterly silent.
But still, there has to be something here.
What's that?
Where the hell am I?
This looks like the inside of some sort of ancient ruin.
Hey!
Hey, Boss Man!
I'm not your Boss Man.
Please just call me Joe.
Boss, come here!
We've got lunch already.
It's time to eat!
I don't care what you say, I'm still not your Boss.
Mr. Boss Man, there's coffee down here for you, too.
Boss or not, I can still have a cup of coffee.
The coffee?
Here, have some.
Yummy, yummy coffee!
This is the coffee?
This is the tool?
Looks like a key.
The biggest key that I've ever seen.
This seems too easy.
I just waltz into a deserted city, grab the magic tool, and walk back out again?
Maybe it's a fake.
If so, it's a good one.
It looks authentic enough to me, anyway.
Hold on.
Slow down!
Maka!
Do you hear me?
Stop running!
I know you want to move fast.
But where are you going?
I don't know.
Nice one.
Probably should have figured out where we were going first.
I know you want to find Medusa and Crona, but you won't do it running around blindly.
You are familiar with the whole look-before-you-leap thing, right?
Yeah.
I know you're right.
Sorry.
So, what do you want to do now?
Well, I can try using my soul perception.
That should sniff out Medusa.
That won't do any good if she has her soul protect on.
True.
But there's still Professor Stein.
And Crona and Miss Marie are out there hunting the witch, too.
If I can find any of their souls, they'll lead me to her.
Lovely.
So now we've got Professor Stein, who even Lord Death couldn't locate.
And then there's Miss Marie and Crona, who went after him.
We're trying to find three people who could be anywhere in the world,
and we don't have a clue where to start looking.
Oh, yeah.
I'm sure that's going to work out perfectly.
Don't be so negative, soul.
I know it's going to work.
Of course.
I'll still need your help.
Uh, sure thing.
Damn it.
I guess this is the security system guarding the tool.
Are you qualified?
Do you have what it takes to wield the magic tool?
Creepy clown.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
Were you the one who destroyed the village?
Answer me.
What am I doing here?
I prevent meddlesome humans from entering this place.
Or from leaving it alive, at least.
I destroy anyone who touches the magic tool.
You're responsible for what happened 20 years ago.
That is correct.
I protect the resting place of the last magic tool.
You killed them all because of the tool?
Those foolish humans.
They dug up this ruin 20 years ago and discovered the tool.
They weren't qualified to wield it either.
So I ate them.
I ate them all.
They were delicious.
All trespassers must die.
That includes you, too.
Snack time.
You won't make a meal out of me that easily.
Running, are you?
I won't let you get barred.
With a huge body like that, he'll never be able to squeeze in after me.
What a poorly designed security system.
Oh, are you stuck?
I'm good!
Close one.
But I did it.
Now I just have to make it back to Liz and Patty.
What's that?
There are two!
Didn't see that coming!
Chow time!
Oink, oink, oink.
Kid sure is taking his time, huh?
There's no reason to worry.
It might take a while, but I'm sure everything will be hunky-dory.
If anyone can do it, it's our meister.
Do it, kid!
I believe in you!
But just to be safe, maybe we should go in there and check up on him.
What, are you kidding me?
We'd be nuts to go into someplace as creepy as that.
Do you have a death wish or something?
It'll be fine.
I say we go in after him.
Seriously?
Were you listening to a thing I just said?
Hm?
Of course I was.
You said something about a pig, right?
Don't you ever listen when I talk!
What's that?
What's what?
I don't know what you're talking about!
I didn't hear anything!
Nothing at all!
Still coming.
I don't know what you're talking about!
Oh!
Perfect symmetry!
No symmetry!
Not symmetrical at all!
No, perfectly symmetrical!
No, not symmetrical at all!
What a perfect pose!
Unbelievable beauty!
The very definition of symmetry!
Oh, dear!
Oh, the destructive power of true beauty!
A little further, just to that building!
Give it back!
Hand over the magic tomb now!
You came after me?
Sure!
What else would we do?
Not so scared of creepy monsters anymore.
Now, Paddy!
Okay!
On it!
You have no right to destroy this village.
You're going to pay for that.
Are you ready for your punishment?
Hand it over, hand it over, hand it over, hand it over now!
These guys aren't easy.
This is bad, kid.
Our shots won't go through.
No!
What now?
You still don't understand the range that you're singing.
I ain't playing.
No way to do it.
It ain't easy to get back to it.
Get your face with a big back drop.
Oh!
Oh, oh!
Mission accomplished.
Unable to activate auto recovery.
System down. Not responding.
Estimated damage received 92%.
Activation time remaining 3 minutes.
It moved? What now?
You who defeated this Guardian, hear me now.
It's different from the voice before. What's going on?
This is a warning. Before you proceed, make certain you have the will to use the magic tool you now possess.
For those who are not qualified, there will be no glory. Only destruction awaits.
Maybe he's right.
Huh?
How can we know for certain that the course we follow is better than the one our enemies have chosen?
Who can promise that the Academy will never use the magic tools with evil intent?
That's it? The thing we were sent here to find?
Yes, and given the level of security set up around it, I'd say my dad's not the only one who thinks it's important.
Okay. So what's he planning to use it for?
That I don't know yet. If I did know, things would be much simpler.
What that robot thing said, is it still bothering you?
Yeah, it is.
Because of that, I'm not sure if handing this over to my dad is the right thing to do.
This is a warning. For those who are not qualified, there will be no glory. Only destruction awaits.
Well then, looks like it's just you and me.
You and me.
¿It is Mr. Bennett?
Thank you.
Here goes.
Ita tsuku taiyou ni
Sada saれて
Atolelu namada ga
Shita daru mabushisa de
Boku o nazou kara
Ta-ri-nai ka-sho ta-da ume-ahu-yo ni
Kimi o mo-to-mete-i-ta
Ture-au new Eittyťto
Homokage no
I no mo
Oogizari no
Mama!
Despite the dangers that lie ahead, they continue on their path.
The woman who would recover her lost partner,
and the boy who would confront his devious mother.
A mismatched pair struggling toward an unknown fate.
What will await them at the end of their journey?
Will they find hope or only more despair?
Hey, who is that?
It's Patty, silly!
On the next episode of Soul Eater,
weakling Krona's determination for you,
for always being by my side.
Patty's here!